<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Home</title>
    <link>/</link>
    <description>Recent content on Home</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-US</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Fri, 11 Dec 2020 00:00:00 +0000</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <item>
      <title>Project 1: Exploratory Data Analysis</title>
      <link>/project/project1/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 11 Dec 2020 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/project/project1/</guid>
      <description>Lance Chu lcc2444  Introduction The main goal of my project is to perform data analysis on NFL team statistics and game attendance by fans by joining a dataset that contains the standings of every NFL team from their 2000-2019 seasons with a another dataset that contains the attendance of viewers for every week from the years 2000-2019. The standings dataset contains the points scored by and against the team, their wins and losses,their playoff/Superbowl status, as well as overall power rankings between the teams.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Project 2: Modeling, Testing, and Predicting</title>
      <link>/project/project2/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 11 Dec 2020 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/project/project2/</guid>
      <description>Lance Chu lcc2444 coffee_ratings &amp;lt;- readr::read_csv(&amp;#39;https://raw.githubusercontent.com/rfordatascience/tidytuesday/master/data/2020/2020-07-07/coffee_ratings.csv&amp;#39;) coffee_ratings &amp;lt;- coffee_ratings %&amp;gt;% select(total_cup_points, species, country_of_origin, harvest_year, variety, processing_method, aroma, flavor, aftertaste, acidity, body, balance, uniformity, clean_cup, sweetness, color, altitude_mean_meters)  0. Introduction The goal of my project is to conduct statistical tests on coffee bean ratings from around the world and to uncover any statistical significance contained within the variables of the coffee dataset by analyzing the relationships between these variables. The coffee dataset contains 1339 observations with many variables, but for my project I have chosen to study 17 variables that are the most useful and easily understood.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Python and R</title>
      <link>/post/2020/12/11/python-and-r/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 11 Dec 2020 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/post/2020/12/11/python-and-r/</guid>
      <description>R Hey everybody welcome to my first blog post. Today I wanted to talk about two coding languages that I learned over the course of this semester. The first one that I learned was R, and it is tremendously useful for data analysis and organizing large sets of data for research. You can check out an awesome example of the power of R through my two projects that you can find by navigating to the projects section of my site or by clicking the links below.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Projects</title>
      <link>/projects/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/projects/</guid>
      <description> Check out some of my coding projects below:
 Wrangling &amp;amp; Exploratory Data Analysis
 Modeling, Inference, Prediction
  -- </description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Resume</title>
      <link>/resume/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/resume/</guid>
      <description>    </description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>
